iosgods.com 2019-11-04

# Privacy Policy - iOSGods

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. iOSGods is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Any information provided by you to iOSGods, by which you can be identified, will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. iOSGods may change this policy as and when necessary. It is your responsibility to check this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure you agree with any changes. If you continue to use our services after such a change, you agree to our updated policy. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**Information Collection And Use**

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you. 

###  Types of Data Collected 

####  Personal Data 

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: 

  * Email address 
  * First name and last name 
  * Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City 
  * Information related to any financial transactions which may be carried out 
  * Cookies and Usage Data 

####  Usage Data 

Additionally, whilst using the iOSGods.com website, any associated websites and sub-domains, some or all of the following information may be collected: 

  * Internet Protocol (IP) address 
  * Geographical location 
  * Browser type and version 
  * Operating system 
  * Referral source 
  * Length of visit, page views, website navigation and any other related browsing activity payment Information such as PayPal, Stripe and/or other third-party payment processors. 

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data. 

####  Tracking & Cookies Data 

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information. 

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service. 

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service. 

For more information regarding the Cookies we set, please read the "Cookies" section of this page. 

**Use of Data**

iOSGods uses the collected data for various purposes: 

  * Access to the iOSGods.com website, associated websites and subdomains 
  * Payments for products or services. We do not collect or save payment information as this is completed via third parties such as PayPal and/or Stripe 
  * To provide and maintain the Service 
  * To notify you about changes to our Service 
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so 
  * To provide customer care and support 
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service 
  * To monitor the usage of the Service 
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues 

**Security Of Data**

We are committed to ensuring that any information you provide to iOSGods is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We give you access to your data via your personal account on iOSGods.com, You can sign up at any time to access, update or delete your personal information. If you wish to have your personal account and personal information deleted on iOSGods.com, you can contact us. 

**Disclosure Of Data**

iOSGods will not sell, distribute or lease your personally identified information to third parties unless we have your explicit permission or are required by law to do so. 

We may use your personally identifiable information to send you security information, product updates, or other information pertaining to iOSGods, or your account. 

We may also disclose information to local authorities if we find that any form of bullying, harassment, terrorism, sexual hate and other crimes that may have been committed or heard of. 

**Links To Other Sites**

iOSGods.com, any associated websites and sub-domains, may contain links to other websites. These websites may or may not be affiliated with iOSGods.  
iOSGods has no control over any external websites therefore clicking any link which results in you visiting an external website will result in this Privacy Policy no longer applying. 

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. 

**Children's Privacy**

Our website, services and contents are not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers. 

**Cookie Policy**

**The Cookies We Set**  
If you create an account with us then we will use cookies for the management of the signup process and general administration. These cookies will usually be deleted when you log out however in some cases they may remain afterwards to remember your site preferences when logged out.

We use cookies when you are logged in so that we can remember this fact. This prevents you from having to log in every single time you visit a new page. These cookies are typically removed or cleared when you log out to ensure that you can only access restricted features and areas when logged in.

In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences. 

More information regarding the Cookies we set can be found here: <https://iosgods.com/cookies/>

 **Third Party Cookies**  
In some special cases we also use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this site.

This site uses the Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.
